<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Radio Stations on Ho Ho Ho!</title>
    <link>/stations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Radio Stations on Ho Ho Ho!</description>
    <image>
      <title>Ho Ho Ho!</title>
      <url>papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/stations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>95.7 BIG FM - Milwaukee, WI</title>
      <link>/stations/957bigfm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/957bigfm/</guid>
      <description>WRIT-FM is a radio station in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, owned by iHeartMedia, Inc.. It carries a variety hits format, switching to Christmas music for much of November and December. The rest of the year, WRIT focuses on hits from the 1980s and 1990s, along with a few &amp;rsquo;60s, &amp;rsquo;70s and early 2000s titles.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1961
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 9 Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer by Dean Martin 9 Carol Of The Bells by David Foster 8 Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas by Luther Vandross 8 All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey 8 Christmas (Baby Please Come Home) by Darlene Love 7 It&amp;rsquo;s Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas by Bing Crosby 7 Winter Wonderland by Amy Grant 7 Rockin&amp;rsquo; Around The Christmas Tree by Brenda Lee 7 Let It Snow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>98.7 - The River - Savannah, GA</title>
      <link>/stations/987theriver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/987theriver/</guid>
      <description> WYKZ is an adult contemporary radio station owned by iHeartMedia, Inc. and licensed to Beaufort, South Carolina, with the branding &amp;ldquo;98.7 The River&amp;rdquo; The station&amp;rsquo;s studio is located on Alfred St. in Savannah, Georgia, and the transmitter is located near Sun City, South Carolina.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1962
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays Sleigh Ride by The Ronettes 10 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 9 Ring Christmas Bells by Ray Conniff 8 Here Comes Santa Claus (Right Down Santa Claus Lane) by Gene Autry 7 Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 7 Rockin&amp;rsquo; Around The Christmas Tree by Brenda Lee 7 It&amp;rsquo;s Beginning to Look Like Christmas by Johnny Mathis 7 Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer by Dean Martin 6 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 6 Run Run Rudolph by Chuck Berry 6 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>99.9 Lite FM - Chicago, IL</title>
      <link>/stations/litefm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/litefm/</guid>
      <description>WLIT-FM is a radio station in Chicago, Illinois, owned by iHeartMedia, Inc. and branded as 93.9 Lite FM. The station has an adult contemporary format playing mostly music from the 1980s to the present day. The station studios are located at the Illinois Center complex on Michigan Avenue in Downtown Chicago, and the transmitter is atop the Willis Tower.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1958
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey 11 Happy Xmas War Is Over (Full Version) by John Lennon 9 It&amp;rsquo;s the Most Wonderful Time of the Year by Andy Williams 9 Rockin&amp;rsquo; Around The Christmas Tree by Brenda Lee 9 Christmas (Baby Please Come Home) by Mariah Carey 9 Here Comes Santa Claus (Right Down Santa Claus Lane) by Gene Autry 8 Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 8 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 8 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 7 White Christmas (feat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KG 95.5 - Sioux City, IA</title>
      <link>/stations/kg95/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/kg95/</guid>
      <description>KGLI is a radio station broadcasting an adult contemporary format. The station serves Sioux City, Iowa, United States, and is owned by iHeartMedia.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1974
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays Sleigh Ride by The Ronettes 9 All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey 8 Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow! by Dean Martin 8 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 8 Rockin&amp;rsquo; Around The Christmas Tree by Brenda Lee 8 Winter Wonderland by Amy Grant 7 Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 7 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 7 It&amp;rsquo;s the Most Wonderful Time of the Year by Andy Williams 7 You&amp;rsquo;re A Mean One, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KOOL 108 - Minneapolis/St. Paul, MN</title>
      <link>/stations/kool108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/kool108/</guid>
      <description> KOOL 108 is Minnesota&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Station. KOOL 108 plays Minnesota&amp;rsquo;s favorite Christmas songs all year long. KOOL 108 is also the home of Minnesota&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas party, the KOOL 108 Jingle Ball.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1968
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays Sleigh Ride by Johnny Mathis 9 Ring Christmas Bells by Ray Conniff 9 Sleigh Ride by The Ronettes 9 Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer by Dean Martin 9 It&amp;rsquo;s the Most Wonderful Time of the Year by Andy Williams 9 Here Comes Santa Claus (Right Down Santa Claus Lane) by Gene Autry 8 Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 8 This Christmas by Train 8 All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey 8 Carol Of The Bells by David Foster 8 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KOST 103.5 - Los Angeles, CA</title>
      <link>/stations/kost1035/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/kost1035/</guid>
      <description> KOST is a commercial radio station in Los Angeles, California. Owned by iHeartMedia, it broadcasts an adult contemporary radio format, switching to Christmas music in early November and playing through New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve. Its studios are co-located with its sister stations on West Olive Avenue in Burbank, CA, and its transmitter is located atop Mount Wilson.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1957
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays It&amp;rsquo;s the Most Wonderful Time of the Year by Andy Williams 10 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 9 Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer by Dean Martin 9 It&amp;rsquo;s Beginning to Look Like Christmas by Johnny Mathis 8 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 8 Carol Of The Bells by David Foster 8 Winter Wonderland by Amy Grant 7 Ring Christmas Bells by Ray Conniff 7 Jingle Bell Rock by Brenda Lee 7 Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer by Burl Ives 6 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic 107 - Orlando, FL</title>
      <link>/stations/magic107/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/magic107/</guid>
      <description>WMGF is a commercial radio station in Mount Dora, Florida, broadcasting to the Orlando area on 107.7 FM. WMGF airs an adult contemporary music format branded as &amp;ldquo;Magic 107.7&amp;rdquo;. The station&amp;rsquo;s studios are located in Maitland and the transmitter tower is in Orange City.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1966
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey 10 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 10 Carol Of The Bells by David Foster 9 This Christmas by Train 9 Holly Jolly Christmas by Michael Bublé 8 Santa Claus Is Coming To Town by The Jackson 5 8 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 8 It&amp;rsquo;s Beginning to Look a Lot like Christmas by Michael Bublé 7 You&amp;rsquo;re A Mean One, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star 102.1 - Dallas and Fort Worth, TX</title>
      <link>/stations/star1021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stations/star1021/</guid>
      <description>KDGE is a radio station licensed to Fort Worth, Texas and serving the Dallas/Fort Worth Metroplex. KDGE is currently owned by iHeartMedia, Inc. and broadcasts a modern rock format to the Dallas/Fort Worth Metroplex. The station&amp;rsquo;s studios are located along Dallas Parkway in Farmers Branch (although it has a Dallas address), and the transmitter site is in Cedar Hill.
Wikipedia
First Aired: 1959
Top Ten Tracks Track Plays Sleigh Ride by The Ronettes 9 Jingle Bells by Frank Sinatra 9 Feliz Navidad by José Feliciano 8 Ring Christmas Bells by Ray Conniff 8 Sleigh Ride by Johnny Mathis 8 Carol of the Bells by Mannheim Steamroller 8 This Christmas by Train 8 White Christmas (feat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
